Guide to the California Asian American Artists Biographical Survey Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- California Artists Files (non-entry artists), Series 2
  - Chang, Frances Y. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Chang, Linda Chen (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Chann, Thomas (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Chau, Ka (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Chen, Stella (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Cheng, Carl Fu Kang (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Cheng, Diana (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Cheng, Kai (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Cheng, Susan (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Chew, Ah (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Chew, June Hon (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Chew, Violet (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Chi, Chen (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Chika, Aki (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Chin, Fong Inong (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Chin, Lin (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Chin, Po (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Chin, Toy (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Ching, Louie (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Chinn, Bing (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Chinn, Jack (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Chinn, Norman (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Chinn, Robert (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Chong, Jerry (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Chow, Raymond J (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Chu, Pearl (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Chuey, Robert (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Chun, Bak (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Chun, Douglas G. (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Chun, Frances (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Chung, Betty (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Chung, Kim (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Chung, Sim (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Coronel, Raul A. (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Date, Henry K. (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Deng, Ming-Dao (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Desota, Raoul A. (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Ding, Jory (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Dohi, Corinne (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Dohi, Ryuichi (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Doi, Geoffrey (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Doi, Shoji (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Dong, Chester (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Dong, Mary (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Endo, H. (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Endo, S. (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Endomoto, Dr. K. (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Esaki, T. (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Estioko, Dalisay E. (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Fang, Chao-ling (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Fang, Keh C. (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Fee, Marcia (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Feng, Gia-Fu (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Fong, Ah-Sing (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Fong, Bund (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Fong, C.W. (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Fong, Chester (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Fong, Dickson (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Fong, Donald (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Fong, Dorothy (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Fong, Edward (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Fong, Foo Lai (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Fong, Freddie (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Fong, Get, Jr. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fong, Get Sr. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Fong, Michael (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Fong, Moi (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Fong, Robert (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Fong, Roger (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Fong, Sam (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Fong, Shirley (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Fong, Thomas (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Fong, Yan-Ting (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Fu, Madeline (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Fugimoto, I. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Fugimoto, Toshizo (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Fujihara, Fuji (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Fujihiro, Harry (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Fujihiro, Y. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Fujii, M. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fujii, Takuichi (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Fujikawa, Fujie (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Fujikawa, Kyoko (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Fujimoto, J. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Fujioka, Henry (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Fujioka, Miye (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Fujita, Akio (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Fujita, Harry (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Fujita, Shozo (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Fujiwara, S. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Fukami, Akira (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Fukuhara, Heizo (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Fukui (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Fukumoto, T. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Fukuoka, Tommy S. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Fukuyama, H. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Fukuyama, K. (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Fung, Edward (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Fung, Henry (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Fung, William (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Furukaki, Sumire (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Furukawa, T. (Ms.) (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Furutani, Brownie (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Furuya, Dorothy M. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Furuya, K. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Furuya, T. (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Furuya, Tomishisa (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Fusaki (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Fushimoto, Toshigo (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Gai Jue (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Galang, Fausto (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Gan, Chester (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Gee, Bing S. (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Gee, Don Goon (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Gee, George E. (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Gee, Margaret M. (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Geiyo, Uyeno (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Gito Moto, Frank (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Gock, Ann Ting, & Co. (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Gock, Hen Yen (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Goda, Lily (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Goldsmith, Narae Mochizuki (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Gong, Fred (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Gong, Robert (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Goo, Ben (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Goto, Clyde (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Goto, George (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Goto, Y. (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Hadeishi, Nobuyuki (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Hajime, Akaike (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Hamada, H. A. (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Hamada, Juzo (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Hamada, Sada (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Hamano, Hakuyo (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Hamaoka, D. (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Hamataka, Ruth (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Hanamura, Midori (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Hara, Kimao (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Hara, Makoto (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Harada, Jiro (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Harada, T. (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Harada, T. (Tom) (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Harada, Yoshiharu (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Haraguchi, Fumi (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Haramaki, Nuiko (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Harano, Earl (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Hasegawa, Aiko (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Hasegawa, Jinwo (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Hasegawa, Madame Sakiko (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Hashimoto, Hateutaro (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Hashimoto, Richard (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Hashioka, Shunichi (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Hata, Frank (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Hatagami, I. S. (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Hatta, Yasutaro (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Hattori (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Hayakawa, George (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Hayashi, (Mrs.) Ichi (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Hayashi, Ichiro (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Hayashi, Midori (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Hayashi, S. (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Hayashi, Shigeru (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Hayashi, T. (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Hayashi, Utaro (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Hayashida, Harry (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Hee, T. (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Hibino, C.T. (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Hidai, Nankoku (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Higa, Y. (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Higashi, Aki (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Hing, Ah (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Hing, Gee (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Hirai, J. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Hirai, Shoj. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Hirai, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Hirano, T. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Hirao, Masataro (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Hirao, Tomosumi (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Hirata, Mas (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Hirose, ?? (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Hirota, Albert (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ho, War Tong (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Hom, Richard (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Homma, P. Y. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Honda, Kaz (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Hong, Edward (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Hori, Daisuke (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Hori, Kaiji (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Hori, Yasuko (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Horibe, Sumi (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Horino, George (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Horiuchi, Milton H. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Horri, Frank S. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Hoshida, George (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Hosoi, Yonekichi (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Hosoi, Yonichio (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Hozumi, D. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Hu, Gee Sun (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Hu, Wai Tse (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Huang, Chester (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Huey, Lock (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Hynes & Co. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Hysong, Joseph L. (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Hyun, Paul (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Hyun, Sam (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Ianaha, K. (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Ichiba, Sam (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Ichien, Masaki (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Ichiyasu, Miyo (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Iguchi, C.S. (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Iiida, K. (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Ikeda, K. (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Ikegawa, Kazuo (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Ikemiya, Jim (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Ikemoto, Howard (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Imai Art Studio (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Imai, Joanne T. (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Imai, Tsunekishi (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Imamura, Niso (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Imashiro (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Imato, Moriseke (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Imazu, Eddie Y. (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Inaba, Shotaro (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Inada, Tom (Mas) (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Ing & Allee Company (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Ing, Maie Ling (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Inokuma, Yoshio (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Inouye, H. (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Inouye, M. (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Inukai, Joey (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Iratani, James (Jiniche) (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Iseyama, Homei (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Ishi, Kofu (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Ishida, Arata Shin (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Ishige, Hoshiko (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Ishigi, Hiroshi (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Ishiguro, C.J. (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Ishihara, T. (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Ishikawa, T. (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Itami, Michi (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Itani, Ichiro (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Itano, Riso (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Itaya, Kinichi (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Ito, Grace (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Ito, H. (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Ito, Jack (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Ito, K. (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Ito, Kiyoshi (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Ito, Shuma (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Ito, Ted (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Ito, Y. (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Itokawa, Takeo (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Iwamoto, Tokutaro (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Iwao, T. (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Iwaso, T. (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Iwata, B. (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Iwata, M. (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Iwata, T. (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Iwata, Walter (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Iwate, Sumiko (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Iwate, Tatsumi (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Iyama, Teruo (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Izumi (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Izumi, Shinsaku (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Izuo Studio (Frank Izuo) (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Izuo, Shigemi (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Jio, Shigenu (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Jo Lo (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Jon-Lee Studio (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Jong, Bill (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Jong, Chock W. (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Jory, Ding (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Jouquin, Mario C. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Jung, Kwan (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Jung, Yee Wah (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Kadowaki, Jin (Frank) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Kai, Jiro (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Kai, Suck (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Kai, Yeiichiro (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Kaiki, A. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Kaito, H.S. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Kaizoji, Jean (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Kaizoji, Sadao (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Kajiyama, Yukio (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Kako, Ryoji (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Kakudo, Howard (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Kamaguchi, Shigira (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Kamei, K. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Kamita, Y. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Kamiyama, Frank Urasaburo (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Kamiyama, Sojui (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Kamiyama, Yukio (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Kanagaki, James (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Kanasawa, Raktin (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Kanasawana, Teziro (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Kanawa, Martha (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Kanazawa, Mrs. K. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Kanda, Tom (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Kaneko, John H. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Kanetsugi, Kenji (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Kaniyama Studio (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Kano, Francis E. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Kasai, Amy (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Katada, Setsuro (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Kataoka, Motoi (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Kato, Kaneshige (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Kato, Masako (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Kato, Mrs. F. (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Kato, Ryoji (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Katsu, S. K. (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Katsurashima, Y. (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Kawachi, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Kawaguchi, Mary (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Kawaguchi, R.T. (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Kawahara, T. (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Kawakami, Chikaji (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Kawakami, K. (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Kawakami, Tomoko (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Kawamorita, Kathryn (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Kawamoto, Dr. K. (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Kawamoto, Roy (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Kawamura, C. (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Kawano, A. (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Kawano, S. (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Kawara, Totaro (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Kawasaki, Torao (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Kawasaki, Toshio (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Kawase, M. (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Kawashima, K. (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Kazuo, M. (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Keat, Miyoko Takeshi (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Kee, Bue (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Kee, Yun Young (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Kei, Mrs. (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Kida, Sahe (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Kido Studio (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Kido, M. (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Kifune, Matsuko (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Kijima, Kenji (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Kikkawa, F. (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Kikuchi, Atsushi (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Kikuchi, M. (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Kim, Bong Tae (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Kim, Lise (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Kim, Maxine (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Kim, Young Suk (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Kimada, Mira (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Kimada, Ray (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Kimishima, Sosaku (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Kimishima, Tosaka (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Kimoto, Diana (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Kimura, Bob (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Kimura, Frank (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Kimura, Hiseo E. (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Kimura, Keichi (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Kimura, Sueko M. (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Kimura, Takeshi (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Kinoshita, Masao (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Kinoshita, Robert (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Kiozumi, Kio (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Kira, Satoshi (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Kirinoe, Setsuo (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Kiro (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Kishi, K. (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Kishi, T. (Ms.) (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Kitagaki-Simioff (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Kitamura, H. (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Kobara, Seiji (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Kobara, Tomi D. (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Kobari, T. (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Kobayashi, Aiko (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Kobayashi, James (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Kobayashi, K. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Kobayashi, Shuko (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Kobayashi, T. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Kobayashi, Teiju (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Kodani, Fumi Mrs. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Kohno, Masako (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Koide, Frank (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Koizumi, Kiyo (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Koizuni, Harry (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Kojima, Joe S. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Kojima, Toshiko (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Kojimoto, Kichiji (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Kokubun, Minotaro (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Komai, H.T. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Komatsu, Toshimune (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Komura, T. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Komuro, David (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Kondo, Henry H. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Kondo, J. M. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Kondo, M. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Kondo, Masao (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Kondo, Seishin (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Koni, T. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Kono, Asahachi (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Kono, S. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Kono, Tadao (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Konomoto (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Konoshita, Robert (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Konya, Paul (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Kosako, Minoru (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Kose, Shoseki (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Kotera, K. (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Koyama, H.T. (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Koyama, R. (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Kuboki, Yasuo (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Kumano, G. H. (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Kumano, George (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Kumano, H.M. (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Kumano, Masasoke (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Kunan, Frank (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Kung, Mary (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Kunishige, Frank (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Kunitsuku (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Kuniwake (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Kurahara, Dick (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Kurahara, Ted (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Kuramatsu, Geichiro E. (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Kurimoto, George C. (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Kurita, Saichi (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Kuroiwa, Chiye (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Kuroka, Tane (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Kuroko Photo Studio (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Kuroko, F.H. (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Kuroshima, Kichisabuo (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Kurushima, Eddy (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Kusama, Henry Teinosuke (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Kushiro, M. (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Kutsunai, K. (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Kuwada, Harry (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Kuwahara, Rokuro (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Kuwashigo, G. (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Kwan, Kwai (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Kwan, Shee (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Kwok, Robert (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Kwok, Wai-Lau (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Kyotow, Ginnosuke (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Kyozan (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Lao, Susan (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Lau, Alvin W. (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Lau, Chun Lum (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Lau, Rosalie Winifred (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Lee, Benn (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Lee, Betty (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Lee, C.Y. (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Lee, Charles Y. (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Lee, Dan (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Lee, Dawson (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Lee, Francis (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Lee, Gayle H. (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Lee, Harry Faung (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Lee, Herbert P. (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Lee, James Richard (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Lee, Jow Y. (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Lee, Lee (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Lee, Leland (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Lee, Leona (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Lee, Luke (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Lee, May (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Lee, Ming-Cho (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Lee, Mrs. (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Lee, Robert (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Lee, Sam (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Lee, Sik-Pang (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Lee, Sui Fong (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Lee, Sun (Yoke Sun) (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Lee, Tong Hoy (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Lee, William (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Lee, Yun Y. (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Lem, Pong N. (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Lem, Richard (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Lem, William (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Leong, Daniel (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Leong, David (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Leong, Look S. (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Leong, Thomas (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Leong, William (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Leung, David T.W. (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Leung, George (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Leung, Louis (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Leung, Monroe (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Lew, Allen (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Lew, Thomas (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Lew, Weyman (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Lew, Wing Tun (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Liang, Fred W. (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Liang, Margaret (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Lienau, Henry (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Lim, Yuen San (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Lin, Sum (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Lin, Ta-Ko (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Linn, Orson (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Little, Po (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Liu, Ronald B. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Lo, Irene (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Long (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Long, David (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Loo, Betty (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Loo, Billie (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Loo, Douglas Y. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Loo, James (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Loo, Victoria M. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Loo, Walter (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Look, Ora Lee (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Look, Wendi S. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Louie, Ernest S. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Louie, George (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Louie, James (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Louie, May (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Low, Frank (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Low, Goodman (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Lowe, Jack (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Low-Suen, Kingland (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Loy, Lillie Tin (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Loy, Lum Wing (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Luke, Jing (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Lum, Eugene (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Lum, Gay Hoy (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Lum, Harry (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Lum, Watson (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Mah, C. F. (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Maimuro, T. (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Maki, Alfred (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Maki, Vera (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Mariyama, S. (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Maru-San Company (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Maruyama, Yoshiro (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Mashino, Shingoro (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Masuda (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Masuda, L. (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Masuda, Sojiro (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Masuko, Motomori (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Masumoto, Teru (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Masuno, T.M. (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Matoi, Takuji (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Matranga, Frank (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Matsuda, F.M. (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Matsueda, Sue (Sueko) (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Matsumato, Tsuyoshi (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Matsumo, Tamaki (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Matsumoto, Aiko (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Matsumoto, Betty (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Matsumoto, Ken F. (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Matsumoto, M. (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Matsumoto, N. (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Matsunami, Kumiko (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Matsuo, James (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Matsuoka, Jack Shigeru (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Matsushita, Kosai, S. (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Matsuura, George (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Matsuzaki, Masako (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Matteo, Maria (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Mayashi, Hiraku (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Mayeda, Torazi (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Mayeda, Yasutada (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Mayo, Ben (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Mazawa, S. (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Mazuika, Sally (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Mei, Barbara (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Midzutani, C. (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Mikami, Charles Erabu (Suiko) (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Mikami, Takahiko (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Mikami, Yerabu (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Minami, Robert (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Minami, Tokusaburo (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Minamoto, S. (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Ming, Him Chio (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Minota, M.K. (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Mirikitani, Tsutomu Jimmy (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Misaki, Arthur (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Mishiura, Arthur (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Mita, Edo (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Mita, Edward (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Mitani, Toda (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Mitsunaga, Edwin (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Miura, Chieka (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Miura, Ichitaro (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Miura, Marna (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Miyagi, Asako Aki (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Miyakawa, Kikuko (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Miyake, J. Z. (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Miyamoto, Asako (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Miyamoto, H.C. (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Miyamoto, Hifumi (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Miyamoto, Mai (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Miyamoto, Mitchie M. (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Miyamoto, Richard (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Miyao, Keijiro (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Miyashiro, Ronald (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Miyata, L.M. (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Miyauchi, Jishiro (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Miyoshi, Hojin (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Mizoguchi (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Mizuhara, Katsui (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Mizuhara, Kikui (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Mizuno, S. (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Mizushima, Hiro (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Mora, Raoul E. (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Mori, Chiye (Loretta) (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Mori, F. (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Mori, Hidei (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Mori, Masao (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Morimoto, I. (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Morimoto, Katsuyo (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Morioka, K. (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Morisawa, K. (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Morita, John Takami (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Morita, K. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Morita, S. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Morita, Yeneji (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Moriyama, Saburo (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Moti, Kaiko (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Motoyoshi, Henry (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Motoyoshi, Paul (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Moy, Philip (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Moy, Seong (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Mukai, George (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Mukai, Tadazo (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mukushina, Rev. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Murakami, Frank H. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Murakami, T. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Murashima, Shimayo (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Murata, Kosetsu (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Murata, Seizo (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Muro, George (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Nabika, Samuel Kuzo (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Nabuhata, Richard (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Nackashima, S. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Nagahama, Isaburo (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Nagahiro, Haruko (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Nagai, Kazuma (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Nagai, Teruo (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Nagana, Minetaro (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Nagano, S. (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Nagano, Yashuhiko (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Nagase, Sam (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Nagashima, Ita (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Nagatomo, Frank (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Nagatomo, Hanbay (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Nagatomo, Joshua (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Nagayama, Toichi (Box 7, Folder 35)